Klemons Brown

Marketing expert

Las Vegas, NV 89101 klemonsbrownramona1@gmail.com 7086820100

To obtain a long term position in your company, while using my 24 years customer service experience and over a year warehouse experience, also have the hard work ethic to become a reliable team player. Always willing to learn new things and stay dedicated.

#readytowork

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

Work Experience

Apppointment setting manager online

K and N Marketing online January 1999 to August 2020

Handle all inbound and outbound campaigns, uploaded leads and revised scripts and Q&A. Trained new employees and made sure team made quota each week. Monitored the floor and answered any disputes and made sure atmosphere stayed positive. But went out of business due to covid 19 and the owners mom passing away. Ramona callum is the owner 7086317046

Kitchen manager/Line cook

Ma barbeque - Chicago, IL November 1996 to July 2020

Grilled fried and and prepare food to order. Trained new employee cooks, scheduled breaks, made sure all stations were stocked, and food was ordered properly. Went out of business due to covid 19

Material Handler/Forklift Operator

Concord Steel - Chicago Heights, IL March 1997 to December 1998

Performed numerous duties and operated overhead cranes inside and outside the building. Company went out of business. Boss Phillip and number is 9048889113

Education

Medical Billing and Coding in progress

Everest University Online

Skills

Cooking Experience (10+ years)

- Sales Experience (10+ years)
- Management Experience (10+ years)
- Microsoft Excel
- Microsoft Word
- Customer Service (10+ years)
- Materials Handling (3 years)
- Forklift (3 years)
- Kitchen Management Experience (10+ years)
- Culinary Experience (10+ years)
- Food Safety (10+ years)
- Food Preparation (10+ years)
- Catering (10+ years)
- Banquet Experience (10+ years)
- Restaurant Management (10+ years)

Certifications and Licenses

Food Handler

May 2019 to May 2024

food handler certificate

ServSafe

Assessments

Restaurant Manager — Familiar

April 2020

Managing restaurant staff and meeting customer expectations.

Full results: Familiar

Customer Focus & Orientation — Proficient

April 2020

Responding to customer situations with sensitivity.

Full results: Proficient

Call Center Customer Service — Familiar

April 2020

Applying customer service skills in a call center setting.

Full results: Familiar

Cooking Skills: Basic Food Preparation — Familiar

April 2020

Preparing food, using cooking equipment, and converting ingredient measurements.

Full results: Familiar

Food Service Fit: Crew Member — Highly Proficient

April 2020

Measures the traits that are important for successful food service crew members.

Full results: Highly Proficient

Verbal Communication — Proficient

April 2020

Speaking clearly, correctly, and concisely.

Full results: Proficient

Retail Skills: Shelf Stocking — Highly Proficient

April 2019

Measures a candidate's ability to monitor and track inventory levels of merchandise on store shelves to maintain supply.

Full results: Highly Proficient

Sales: Influence & Negotiation — Completed

April 2020

Persuading reluctant customers to buy products or services, and influencing and negotiating with customers to meet sales goals.

Full results: Completed

Attention to Detail — Familiar

June 2019

Identifying differences in materials, following instructions, and detecting details among distracting information.

Full results: Familiar

Food Safety — Familiar

November 2019

Proper food handling, storage, and equipment use for preventing the spread of foodborne illness.

Full results: Familiar

Work Style: Reliability — Familiar

October 2019

Tendency to be dependable and come to work.

Full results: Familiar

Indeed Assessments provides skills tests that are not indicative of a license or certification, or continued development in any professional field.